fareharbor.com 2019-10-27

# Privacy Policy | FareHarbor

**Aloha! Our team here at FareHarbor Holdings, Inc. (“FareHarbor”) values your trust, and makes it a high priority to ensure the security and confidentiality of the personal information you provide to us. Below you will find our Privacy Policy. We encourage you to please read our policy to learn about our privacy practices so you can better understand what we collect from you, why we collect it and your rights. Remember, by visiting our website or using our services, you are accepting our practices. Mahalo!**

## What information do we collect?

We collect personally identifiable information from you when you register on our site, place a reservation order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form or input data on our site in any way.

When booking reservations through or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information, social security number, gender, certification level, experience level, height, weight, shoe or other clothing size, hotel information, or other information as requested by the companies that use our service. You may, however, visit and browse our sites and offerings and not enter any of your personally identifiable information.

## How do we use your information?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * **To personalize your experience** (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * **To improve our website** (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * **To improve customer service** (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * **To process transactions** (In addition to processing your bookings with the companies that use our services, the email address you provide during booking processing may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your reservation, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information.
  * **To provide services to the companies that use FareHarbor**
  * **To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature**
  * **To send periodic emails**

We also may collect and store information about you that we receive from other sources to, among other things, enable us to verify, update and correct the information contained in our databases, prevent fraud, provide services to our other clients, and to better customize your experience on our site.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future marketing emails, please contact [customerservice@fareharbor.com](mailto:customerservice@fareharbor.com).

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to help maintain the safety of your personal information when you reserve a booking or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

All supplied credit card information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. This information is then encrypted in our payment provider’s systems, may only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and they are required to keep the information confidential. Please understand that while we try our best to safeguard your personal information once we receive it, no transmission of data over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

After a transaction, your personal information may be kept on file in order to archive reservation data, help improve the customer experience, and for other business purposes.

## Do we use cookies and interest-based advertising?

Yes, cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements, market our services, and compile data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use any personally identifiable information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct, improve or market our business.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still reserve a booking over the telephone by contacting the company’s customer service number directly. Your browser or device may include “Do Not Track” functionality. FareHarbor’s information collection and disclosure practices and the choices we provide, will continue to operate as described in this Privacy Policy, whether or not a Do Not Track signal is received.

We allow third-party advertising companies to collect certain information when you visit our site. These companies may utilize cookies, pixels or other technologies to collect and use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., hashed data, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you (i.e. interest-based advertising). They may also use persistent identifiers to anonymously track your Internet usage over time and across other websites in their networks beyond our site. To learn more about interest-based advertising or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit the websites of the Digital Advertising Alliance at [http://aboutads.info](http://aboutads.info/) and Networking Advertising Initiative at <http://networkadvertising.org/choices>. Google, as a third-party vendor, also uses cookies to serve ads. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads based on your visits to FareHarbor’s sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

Yes, we provide your information to the third-party companies that use our service to book online reservations. We share information about your reservation and also may include information about how you use and interact with our site, such as your reservation history, which activities you like or are recommended for you, and other information. In some cases, we may provide these third-party companies with analytics and other information about your interaction with our service via their website. Please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to those third-party companies and FareHarbor is not responsible for how they use, maintain or disclose your information.

We also use third-party service providers who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site’s policies, or protect our or others rights, property, or safety in anyway legally or most appropriate to the situation at our sole discretion.

We may share your personal information with our business partners or co-marketers from time to time. Although our treatment of your personal information is governed by this Privacy Policy, the third party’s treatment of your information will be governed by their privacy policy. Non-personally identifiable or aggregated information may also be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Third-party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## California Residents

California law permits California residents to request certain information regarding FareHarbor’s disclosure of their personally identifiable information to third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [privacy@fareharbor.com](mailto:privacy@fareharbor.com) specifying that you seek your “California Customer Choice Notice.” Please allow up to thirty days for a response.

All users of our site may update their information at any time by logging into their control panel and going to the ‘Edit Profile’ page. We reserve the right to not accommodate a request to change your information if we believe doing so would violate any law or legal requirement, or cause the information to be incorrect.

## Children’s Information

FareHarbor’s sites are a general audience websites and do not offer services directed to children. You must be 16 years of age or older to book using FareHarbor’s sites. Should a child whom we know to be under 13 send personal information to us, we will use that information only to respond directly to that child to inform him or her that we must have parental consent before receiving his or her personal information and will delete the information. Bookings made by underage individuals without consent will not be honored. If you believe that FareHarbor has been provided with the personal information of a child under 13 without parental consent, please notify us immediately at [customerservice@fareharbor.com](mailto:customerservice@fareharbor.com).

## Use of Stripe

Information about our use of Stripe for payment services can be found here.

## Visiting our website from outside the United States

If you are visiting our site or using our services from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States. The data protection and other laws of the United States might be different from those in your country, but please be assured that we take steps to ensure that your privacy is protected in accords with this policy. By using our services and voluntarily submitting your information to us, you consent to the general use of such information as provided in this Privacy Policy and to the transfer of that information to and storage of that information in the United States. For individuals in the European Economic Area or Switzerland, please [click here](https://fareharbor.com/legal/privacy-shield) to find out more information.

## Additional Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our [Terms of Use](https://fareharbor.com/legal/tos/) which establishes the use, disclaimers, limitations of liability, and other terms and conditions governing the use of our site and services at <https://fareharbor.com/legal/tos/>. This Privacy Policy is made a part of and incorporated into our Terms of Use; any capitalized terms used but not defined in this policy shall have the same meanings as set out in the Terms of Use.

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use.

## Assignment

We may change our ownership or corporate organization while providing our sites or services. We may also sell certain assets associated with the sites or services. As a result, please be aware that in such event we may transfer some or all of your information to an entity acquiring all or part of our assets or to another entity with which we have merged. Under such circumstances we would, to the extent possible, require the acquiring party to follow the practices described in this Privacy Policy, as it may be amended from time to time. Nevertheless, we cannot promise that the acquiring or merged company will have the same privacy practices or treat your information the same as described in this Privacy Policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify or amend the terms of this Privacy Policy from time to time. Your continued use of our sites or services following the posting of changes will mean you accept the new Privacy Policy as modified. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page and they will be effective immediately.

This policy was last modified on April 12, 2018.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

FareHarbor Holdings, Inc.  
P.O. Box 306 Wayzata, MN 55391 USA  
(855) 495-4333
